I am going to your aunt's place.
Ok?  If someone is complaining then
both of you will not go out.  Bye-B come soon.
Brother, I am feeling very hungry.
I am also feeling hungry.  Wait a minute, did mom
make something?
No, mom did not make anything.
I feel like mom avoids cooking.
So what to make now?
Hey, let's make chicken.   Do
you love your life or not?  Otherwise, is it
from mommy's hands?
Hey crazy, it's not real chicken.  I want to
make this soybean chicken.   Yes yes
ok.
Like the edge of a book, like soap foam.
Like there is
no drink more fragrant than Billu in the whole world
[music] You don't have such a name
Bhaiya Mummy has come
[screaming sound]
Baba I am throwing away bowl after bowl Papa
₹000
You will not eat it in the mind